babyrazzi.com 2010-09-27

# Privacy Policy > Babyrazzi – Celebrity Baby Blog & Pregnancy News

The establishment of trust and privacy is instrumental to the welfare of the internet and the relationship between people and the web sites they visit. In addition, the collection, use, and transfer of information serves to enhance the usefulness of the internet, provided that such information is handled in a fair and responsible manner. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by www.babyrazzi.com and how it is used. In this privacy policy, “personal information” means information relating to an individual and which identifies that individual, either directly or indirectly, such as your name or email address. Please review this document so you can be aware of how your privacy may be affected by visiting this web site. If you have any questions or comments on this policy, please feel free to contact us.

**Log Files**

Like most web sites, www.babyrazzi.com makes use of log files. The information contained in log files includes visitors’ internet protocol (IP) addresses, types of web browser, Internet Service Providers (ISPs), date and time of visits, referring/entrance/exit pages, and number of clicks. This data is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track visitors’ movement through the site, and to gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any data that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies & Web Beacons**

www.babyrazzi.com uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record visitor-specific information on which pages the visitors access or visit, customize web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Blogads, Google AdSense, ValueClick Media, and Adbrite. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to display the advertisements and links that appear on www.babyrazzi.com which are sent directly to your browser. These third-party ad servers or ad networks automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content you see. www.babyrazzi.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices, as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.babyrazzi.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser’s options. More detailed information about cookie management with a specific web browser can be found at the browser’s web site or in its help documentation.

Google AdSense makes use of the DoubleClick DART cookie which enables it to serve ads to our visitors based on their visit to www.babyrazzi.com and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Outbound Links**

Links to third-party sites are provided by www.babyrazzi.com. www.babyrazzi.com is not responsible for the content or management of these third-party sites. Please consult the privacy policies of these third-party web sites for their privacy practices.

**Communication**

By sending an email to the owner of www.babyrazzi.com, you may reveal personal information about yourself, including your email address. This personal information will not be shared with third-parties, nor will it be used to send you unsolicited communications.

**Notification of Changes to this Policy**

To check for updates on this policy, please consult this page. This policy was last updated on March 12, 2009.

If you require further information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://babyrazzi.com/contact-us/ "Contact Babyrazzi").
